Page({
  data: {
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Hello world <3',
        answer: '2017.3.26'
      },
      {
        question: '奶瓶品牌？',
        answer: 'NUK'
      },
      {
        question: '奶粉？',
        answer: '喜乐'
      },
      {
        question: '出生医院？',
        answer: '北京天坛医院'
      },
      {
        question: '害怕？',
        answer: '扫地机器人'
      },
      {
        question: '喜欢？',
        answer: '吃尽'
      },
      {
        question: '最近看的书？',
        answer: 'Brown bear'
      },
      {
        question: '最喜欢的歌？',
        answer: 'Ponytail'
      },
      {
        question: '学习？',
        answer: 'Ready Go'
      },
      {
        question: '走路咋样？',
        answer: '着急的时候还是喜欢爬'
      }
    ]
  }
})
